While we're waiting for the next truck to appear
我们在等待第二辆卡车的时候
some of the younger cowboys rope up a bull for practice
一些年轻的牛仔们抓了一匹公牛
as the rodeo season is about to start.
来玩一个叫做Rodeo的游戏（牛仔骑术表演）
Vanderley is a budding rodeo star and makes it look deceptively easy.
范德雷是一个骑术高手 他看起来轻松自如
They just saddled up a rodeo show for themselves
他们只是自娱自乐
and then some bright spark looked at me and said, 'oi, do you want to have a go?'
但一会他们便过来怂恿我 试试吧
Hand in here.
抓住这儿
OK, and then?
好的 然后呢
Squeeze here?
夹紧这儿
And squeeze here.
And then just...
然后
Well, just...stupid question, really, isn't it?
哈哈 真是愚蠢的问题
What are you supposed to do? Grip, hold on and grip!
你建议我怎么做？抓紧绳子 抓紧就好
Well, there you go.
好的 游戏开始
OK, OK.
好的 好的
Right, here?
腿放在这儿么
And when I fall off, which I will...
那要是掉下来的话 那我会……
Just let go. And fall, then...
别紧张 摔了就松绳子
Ah, ah, ow!
哦
That hurt!
好痛啊
Argh!
啊
That properly hurt.
痛死我了
That was about two seconds on the rodeo. Whoo!
在牛背上呆了大概2秒
That hurt! Ow! My last day of being a cowboy.
太疼了 喔 作为牛仔的最后一天
and I think... Good way to leave it, really.
这倒是一个完美的结局方式
Leave it to the big boys, the real cowboys.
还是让真正的年轻牛仔们去玩吧
The trucks are eventually loaded and we all head off.
卡车载着我们...
到达了兴古河维多利亚港的牛肉出口点
to the cattle port of Victoria
on the Xingu River.